jrank.org 2013-05-19

# Free Site Search Engine - put a search engine on your web site or add search to your blog

## Information we collect

**From the end user** : JRank collects the IP address and query data from every visitor to each JRank site search instance and the JRank website itself. Although we collect query data, we do so for statistical purposes only. Absolutely no personal data of any kind is collected, extracted, or stored from individual search queries. Aggregate query data is provided to each site search user in control of their respective site search instances.

**From the site search user** : JRank collects personal information such as your email, password, and IP address, as well as all additional data describing a website for the creation of a "context". Such information is stored only for the purposes of identifying and authenticating each user and providing statistical and administrative data to the operators of JRank. Your personal data, such as your email address and password, will not be sold nor redistributed to any third party at any time.

## Your rights as a site search user

As a user and member of JRank's site search engine web software, you may, at any time, cancel your account. Once your account has been cancelled, your email address, password, website data, and search statistics associated with your site search "context" instances will be removed from JRank. Once removed, your data cannot and will not be restored. However, JRank may still retain your data in backups and log files for a limited period of time.

## Updates to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, this Privacy Policy may be modified. Updates will be posted in place of this Privacy Policy and will remain accessible to all users of the JRank website. By using the JRank website, a user is bound by any and all changes that are posted. If, however, JRank changes its Privacy Policy in order to access, collect, or store users' personal data in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will post a notice on our website for 30 (thirty) days.
